What I would like to do in the future
Now, let's see what Aira would like to do in the future!
What is the third and final one?
Here is the third one!
Ta-da!
Live streaming on AmeFlash for 24 hours a day!
Would you like to do this?
Yes, I would.
Momoguro-san used to do it, right?
That was so much fun, and Rainflash has a very unusual group of people, a unique group of people.
So, even if you do a one or two hour show, it's still watchable, but you have to spend more time on it,
But I think you have to spend more time to bring out the interesting parts of the show,
If you deliver for 24 hours, you can see what happens when you get sleepy,
I thought that if we streamed for 24 hours, people would be able to see what happens when they fall asleep, or how bad or good they are at waking up from sleep, and I thought that everyone would enjoy watching these things,
I'd like to do this for a long time.
The members are doing it, too.
Really?
But if you wait 24 hours, you can do a lot of things.
What would you like to do?
There's one thing I'd really like to do.
I want to barbecue for sure.
Surprises in your sleep?
I want to set it up.
I want to do it.
I want to do something where the members are sleeping.
I want to do a Guinness challenge. You want to set me up? I want to do something where the members are sleeping.
Or a Guinness challenge.
Oh, something like that, a Guinness challenge.
I would like to do something like that, or make something. It would be nice to have time for live performances,
That's exactly what the members, for example, tried to compose a song by humming.
Improvise and sing a song.
or karaoke.
I would like to do all kinds of things.
If we were to do it for 24 hours a day, I'm sure I'd get very sleepy.
I'm sure I'd get very sleepy.
Are you confident that you would wake up?
I'm not.
No?
I can sleep anywhere.
I can sleep no matter how loud it is.
I think I'll probably sleep through the stream.
With the camera rolling? The camera?
Giggle, giggle, giggle.
But I think Moika is worse.
When you say she sleeps...
Is it okay to call her sleeping face?
Maybe.
But she looks terrible.
Really?
Suzuki, Suzuki, Suzuki...
Is it heavy?
It's like this when you sleep in the car.
Yes, they do.
Their faces are terrible.
From a distance...
I don't know... from a distance...
You can't tell.
Some of the members are very particular.
Okay, I'll go with the long view.
Maybe I'm not getting enough sleep.
I see.
Let's do it together.
Let's do it.
Let's do it together in the 20th period.
Great, I'm sorry to bother you.
In that 24 hours...
Let's do it.
Let's do it in the night time. Let's do it at night.
Is that okay? I want to do it. I want to do it.
Let's do it. It's a dream come true, isn't it? If you decide to do it, please let me know as soon as possible.
I'll let you know as soon as it's decided. I'd love to do it.
Yes, I'll be there. I'll be participating at night as well.
I look forward to working with you.
Yes, I will. I look forward to working with you.
What I would like to do in the future, participation!
What I would like to do in the future, participate!
What is this program?
Mr. Toa,
Tuffy,
Kari Tamago
Yoshida-san,
and Mr. Toi. Thank you very much. Thank you for watching!